<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<task id="NetworkExplorer-CreateCustomTopology">
    <title>Create Private Network</title>
    <taskbody>
        <prereq>
            <p>
                To create a Private Network, you must have a user
                account with one of the following roles:
                <ul>
                    <li>Network_Explorer_Administrator</li>
                    <li>Network_Explorer_Operator</li>
                </ul>
            </p>
            <p>
                <b>Note:</b>
                To check the currently assigned roles, select the <b>User ID</b> on the top right hand corner, and click
                <b>View User Profile</b> from the drop-down list. The assigned roles are displayed.
            </p>
            <p>
                If you do not have the required roles, contact the System Administrator.
            </p>
        </prereq>
        <context>
            <p>
                <b>Objective</b>
            </p>
            <p>
                This tutorial describes the steps required to create a Private Network.
                A Private Network is a grouping of Network Elements that can be associated together for a particular purpose,
                For example by company, project or location.
            </p>
        </context>
        <steps>
            <step id="1">
            <cmd> Select Required Collection </cmd>
            <info>
                <ul>
                    <li>Launch <xref href="#topologybrowser" scope="external">Topology Browser</xref>.
                    </li>
                    <li>Select a <b>Custom Topology</b> from the <b>Topology</b> drop down.</li>
                    <li>
                        Select Required Collection.
                        <p>
                            <b>Note:</b>
                            If no collections exist, select the root of <b>Custom Topology</b>.
                        </p>
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </info>
        </step>
            <step id="2">
                <cmd> Create a Private Network </cmd>
                <info>
                    <ul>
                        <li>Click <b>Create a Private Network</b>. The <b>Create a Private Network</b> fly-out panel is displayed.</li>
                        <li>Enter required information in the fly-out panel. For more information, see <xref href="../userinterface.xml#createAPrivateNetworkFlyout" type="concept">Create a Private Network Fly-out</xref>.</li>
                        <li>Click <b>Create</b>. The collection is added to the <b>Custom Topology</b> tree and automatically selected.</li>
                    </ul>
                </info>
            </step>
        </steps>
        <result>
            <p>The newly created Private Network is displayed in the <b>Topology</b> drop-down and tree.</p>
        </result>
    </taskbody>
</task>