<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<task id="Associated_NetworkElements">
    <title>View associated Network Elements</title>
    <taskbody>
        <prereq>
            <p>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        There are nodes synchronized on ENM.
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        The ENM user must have read rights for Topology Browser.
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </p>
        </prereq>
        <context>
            <p>
                <b>Objective</b>
            </p>
            <p>
                When Topology Browser is accessed from the Launcher page, the full topology tree is shown by default.
                The user can browse and locate a Managed Object through either the top level SubNetworks or
                the '<b>All Other Nodes</b>' branch.
                In order to view the associated Network Element of an MeContext or ManagedElement, the user must locate
                and return the object through Network Explorer.
                An example of this process is given in this tutorial.
            </p>
            <p>
                <b>Outline</b>
            </p>
            <ol>
                <li>
                    <xref href="#1">Select an MeContext MO</xref>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <xref href="#2">Open Network Explorer</xref>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <xref href="#3">Enter Search Criteria</xref>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <xref href="#4">Search for Network Elements</xref>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <xref href="#5">Return results to Topology Browser</xref>
                </li>
            </ol>
        </context>
        <steps>
            <step id="1">
                <cmd>Select an MeContext MO</cmd>
                <info>
                    <ul>
                        <li>Open the <b>Topology Browser</b> page and select an MeContext Managed Object from the tree.</li>
                    </ul>
                        <image href="/resources/images/TopologyBrowserMeContext.png" alt="Select MeContext"/>
                </info>
            </step>
            <step id="2">
                <cmd>Open Network Explorer</cmd>
                <info>
                    <ul>
                        <li>After noting the objects name, click the <b>Search for an Object</b> link from the Action Bar.</li>
                    </ul>
                        <image href="/resources/images/ObjectSearch.png" alt="Object Search"/>
                </info>
            </step>

            <step id="3">
                <cmd>Enter Search Criteria</cmd>
                <info>
                    <ul>
                        <li>Enter '<b>NetworkElement</b>' into the Network Explorer input box.</li>
                    </ul>
                        <image href="/resources/images/NetworkExplorer.png" alt="Network Explorer"/>
                </info>
            </step>

            <step id="4">
                <cmd>Search for Network Elements</cmd>
                <info>
                    <ul>
                        <li>Click the <b>Search</b> button and wait for results.</li>
                        <li>A table with a list of Network Elements will display. Click the checkbox of the Network Element
                            associated with the Managed Object from step 1 above.
                            To return to the Topology Browser page click the '<b>Locate in Topology</b>' button in the Action Bar
                            and Topology Browser will open in a new browser window (enable popups in the browser if required).
                            Alternatively, it is also possible to select the '<b>Return Selected Managed Object</b>' button
                            located on the bottom bar, which will return to the App which called Network Explorer (in this case,
                            Topology Browser).</li>
                    </ul>
                        <image href="/resources/images/NetworkExplorerInput.png" alt="Network Explorer Input"/>
                </info>
            </step>

            <step id="5">
                <cmd>Return results to Topology Browser</cmd>
                <info>
                    <ul>
                        <li>When the Topology Browser page opens, it is possible to view the Network Element associated with the
                            MO on the Topology Tree. The Topology Tree will not show the Full Network Tree when displaying
                            Network Elements, as they are located on opposite sides of the ENM Base Model.</li>
                    </ul>
                        <image href="/resources/images/NetworkExplorerOutput.png" alt="Network Explorer Output"/>
                </info>
            </step>

        </steps>
    </taskbody>
</task>
